unhaggle.com 2011-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Unhaggle.com

## Privacy Policy

 _Updated on January 7, 2011_

Unhaggle is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to this Site. This Privacy Policy applies to the Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites to which we link. You agree that your use of the Site signifies your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you are not authorized to use this Site.

 **Information Collected** : In order to access this Site, you must first complete the registration process. During the registration process, we collect personal information such as your name and email address. Once you complete and submit your registration, you have opted-in to receive email communication from Unhaggle.

We also collect personal information when you choose to use certain other features of the Site, such as making purchases, we require you to provide additional information such as your phone number, billing addresses and credit card information, and we may request additional personal information such as your shopping preferences and demographics.

In addition, we automatically gather certain information about the use of the Site, such as how frequently certain areas of the Site are visited, including through the use of cookies, web beacons and other technologies. Most browsers can be set to prevent cookies or to notify you when one is being placed. However, cookies are necessary to access the Site.

 **How We Use Your Information** : We will not share or disclose your information to anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use personally identifiable information in order to give you a more enjoyable convenient shopping experience and to help us identify and/or provide information, products or services that may be of interest to you. We use your personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of the Site and its features, including without limitation: fulfilling your order; providing customer service; tracking email invitations you send; and otherwise supporting your use of the Site. We may also track your past purchases to provide you with a personalized profile of your shopping history. In addition, we may notify you about new services or special promotional programs, or send you offers or information.

In connection with the performance of services to maintain and operate the Site and certain features on the Site, certain trusted third parties may be permitted to access your information. For example, we may use third parties to host the Site; operate various features available on the Site; send emails; analyze data; provide search results and links and assist in fulfilling your orders.

We may transfer personally identifiable information as an asset in connection with a proposed or actual merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in control. In such a circumstance the Transferee would be bound by the terms of this privacy policy.

We reserve the right to disclose information in order to comply with a subpoena, court order, administrative or governmental order, or any other requirement of law, or when we, in our sole discretion, believe it is necessary in order to protect our rights or the rights of others, to prevent harm to persons or property, to fight fraud and credit risk reduction.

We use non-personally identifiable information in the aggregate, so that we can improve the Site and for business and administrative purposes. We may also use or share with third parties for any purpose aggregated data that contains no personally identifiable information.

 **How We Protect Your Information** : We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

The Site encrypts your credit card number and other personal information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology to provide for the secure transmission of the information from your PC to our servers. In addition, only those employees and third parties who need access to you information in order to perform their duties are allowed such access.

 **Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information and Preferences** : If you are a registered user, you may access and update your registration information and your preferences to receive email or other communications from us by sending an email to [contact@unhaggle.com](mailto:contact@unhaggle.com). Any user who receives an email invitation to join the Site may choose not to receive such invitations in the future by following the instructions in the email invitations and, in addition, if you are a member, you may also choose not to receive such invitations by changing your preferences as indicated above. In addition, you may update or change your personal information or preferences by sending an email to [contact@unhaggle.com](mailto:contact@unhaggle.com). We will take commercially reasonable steps to implement your opt-out requests promptly, but you may still receive communications from us for up to ten business days as we process your request.

While we make efforts to accommodate requests to restrict our use of your information, we reserve the right to delete all or any portion of customer information if we are not able to reasonably accommodate a requested restriction.

 **Children's Privacy and Parental Controls** : We do not solicit any personal information from children. If you are not 18 or older, you are not authorized to use the Site. Parents should be aware that there are parental control tools available online that you can use to prevent your children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors.

 **Privacy Policy Changes** : If we decide to change our Privacy Policy for the Site, we will post the revised Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we may disclose it to anyone. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Unhaggle Inc.   
3585 Laird Road, Unit #3   
Mississauga, ON L5L 5Z8
